Sorry, I should've seen that.
(Howard:)I'll get out of your way.
Uh, you're gonna wanna eat those eggs
while they're still hot.
(Raj:)Thank you.
And there's lox and cream cheese
in the fridge.
(Leonard:)The bagels are in the oven.
I was warming them up.
(Penny:)That's great.
I'm just gonna hang out with my mom.
That's always fun.
(Howard:)Good.
[BOTH SIGH]
(Penny:)-Are we terrible people?
-I don't know.
(Leonard:)What do you want me to do?
Ahh. Get him. Bring him back.
(Leonard:)You sure?
(Howard:)Yeah.
(Leonard:)Okay. Howard, come back.
(Howard:)Oh, you guys had me scared
for a minute.
No, no. That rate is much too low from
what we'd expect from this collision.
Do you understand we're talking about
dark matter colliding in outer space?